Wrege, Charles Collection of Midvale Steel Company Index Cards 6304
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Charles Wrege Collection of Midvale Steel Company Index Cards
1864-1969
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wrege, Charles D.
6304
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
This is a collection of index cards with notes on some of the events and history of the Midvale Steel Company.
6986423
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 14, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Charles "Chuck" Wrege finished his undergraduate degree in Upsala College, obtained his Masters degree at the New School fo Social Research and another Masters of Business Administration and his Ph.D. at NYU. He taught industrial management at Rutgers University for 30 years. He became a renowned historian, researcher and writer. He is regarded as a "National Treasure" by many in his field because of his expertise and the seminal research he has done in the area of management history.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Wrege, Charles D.; Midvale Steel Company
6986423
- Midvale Steel Company S-2, 1864-1920 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Midvale Steel Company - Photocopies of index Cards - B, 1915-1916 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Midvale Steel Company - Photo copies of index cards - C, 1867-1921 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Midvale Steel Company - Photocopies of index cards - D, 1882-1890 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Midvale Steel Company - Photocopies of index cards - E, 1870-1918 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Midvale Steel Company F, 1866-1921 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Midvale Steel Company G, 1888-1924 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Midvale Steel Company H, 1867-1887 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Midvale Steel Company I, 1889-1924 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Midvale Steel Company J, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Midvale Steel Company K, 1887-1916 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Midvale Steel Company L, 1870-1917 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Midvale Steel Company - Photo copies of index cards - A, 1886-1915 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Midvale Steel Company N-R, 1864-1918 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Midvale Steel Company P-, 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Midvale Steel Company, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Midvale Steel Company, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Midvale Steel Company M-O, 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Midvale Steel Company P-R, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Midvale Steel Company S-, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Midvale Steel Company T,V,W-2, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Midvale Steel Company A-B, 1915-1919 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Midvale Steel Company C-D, 1915-1916 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Midvale Steel Company, 1916-1921 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Midvale Steel Company G-K, 1867-1921 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Midvale Steel Company L-O, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Midvale Steel Company M-Mc, 1867-1916 (Box 1, Folder 13)